all-bookmark.info 2017-07-30

# Privacy Policy - Pennistone Media

Pennistone Media Privacy Policy

 This document outlines how we collect, use and protect your information on this website (<http://www.pennistonemedia.com/>).

 **What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you fill out a form. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

 **What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: To process transactions and send newsletters or contact you for requested purposes. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

 **How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

 **Do we use cookies?**  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

 **​Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise, transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  
 **  
Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the All Online Privacy Protection Act. We, therefore, will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.  
 **  
Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act); we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products, and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.  
 **  
Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.  
 **  
Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.  
This policy was last modified on 18/08/2016  
 **  
​Contacting Us**  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may [contact us](http://www.pennistonemedia.com/#contact) here:
